gapinc.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy

The privacy policy below governs your use of **gapinc.com,** the Gap Inc. corporate website. To review the privacy policies that apply to customers of **Gap Inc.'s brands** , please click on the following links:

[Gap](http://www.gap.com/customerService/info.do?cid=2331&mlink=5058,2486832,emailreg&clink=2486832)[  
Banana Republic](http://bananarepublic.gap.com/customerService/info.do?cid=1330&mlink=5001,2486830,15&clink=2486830)  

At Gap Inc., we respect the privacy of all visitors who access and use our corporate Web site. The information we collect on this site is used to understand how we can enhance our site and improve your experience. This policy describes the limited circumstances in which we collect personal information, why we collect it and how we use it. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. This policy is for gapinc.com only and does not apply to the gap.com, bananarepublic.com, oldnavy.com, piperlime.com or athleta.com sites. You can visit any of those sites to read about their specific privacy policies.

If our information practices change in the future, we will post an updated policy on this Web site. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.  

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at custserv@gap.com, or write to us at Gap Inc., Attn: Corporate Communications, Two Folsom Street, San Francisco, California 94105.

**What kind of information does Gap Inc. collect?**  
We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, etc., when you visit our website, apply for a job, or contact us with a question or concern.

**How does Gap Inc. use my information?**  
We may use your personal information in the following ways:

• | To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our company, our Social Responsibility Program, employment opportunities for which you've applied, and other topics we think may be of interest to you  
---|---  
• | To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services  
• | To analyze trends and statistics  
• | To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business  
• | To contact you if necessary  
  
You always have the choice not to receive information or communications from us. For instructions on opting out, please see the section entitled, "How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?", below.

If you are interested in a job at Gap Inc. or any of its affiliates and you choose to send your resume to us through this website or via fax or mail, we will maintain and use the information contained in your resume for recruiting purposes only. If you choose to apply for a job online, we will collect information about your work history, your education and how to contact you. Again, we maintain and use this information for recruiting purposes only.

**Does Gap Inc. share my information?**  
We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us to third parties. However, we do contract with service providers to assist us in maintaining and managing our databases and to communicate with those who are interested in our company. We do not authorize any of those third parties to make any other use of your information. We also may use aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about you to enhance our site. Additionally, we may disclose and maintain user information in special cases, including:

• | In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, we will disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy  
---|---  
• | If necessary, in our good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Gap Inc. or others.  
  
**How do I access or change my information?**  
You can ask us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below. Please note that any request to update your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and 6-8 weeks for your postal mail request.

**How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?**  
Gap Inc. wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us.  If you prefer not to receive promotional information or other communications from us, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Gap Inc.

**How does Gap Inc. protect kids' privacy?**  
Gap Inc. is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our websites are general audience sites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children.

**How does Gap Inc. use cookies?**  
We make limited use of cookies on this Web site. A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies for the limited purpose of determining whether you have visited a particular page before, so that you will not have to view introductory information that is played for first-time visitors. We do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.

**How does Gap Inc. use pixel tags?**  
We may use "pixel tags" (also called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our websites and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our visitors' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our websites. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our sites may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the sites. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

**How do I know my personal information is secure?**  
We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

**What is "phishing"?**  
"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

**What about links to other websites?**  
Please remember that the privacy policy stated here applies only to the gapinc.com website.  Our online shopping sites (gap.com, bananarepublic.com, oldnavy.com, piperlime.com, and athleta.com) have their own privacy policies. In addition, this site may contain links to other third-party sites that are provided solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. We do not control the privacy policies or practices of these third-party sites and are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites. You should review those policies before providing any personal information.

**How do I contact you?**  
For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional or other communications, or to update your personal information, you can contact us by email at custserv@gap.com, or write to us at Gap Inc., Attn: Corporate Communications, Two Folsom Street, San Francisco, California 94105.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Gap Inc. who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

Gap Inc. - California Privacy Rights  
Legal Department  
2 Folsom Street  
San Francisco, CA 94105
